<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog | K C Sreevasthavan</title>
    <description>This blog is maintained by K C Sreevasthavan. You can find interesing tutorials, free resources(themes, tips, designs), articles, music etc here.</description>
    <link>https://vasthav.github.io/</link>
    <atom:link href="https://vasthav.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jan 2019 08:06:42 +0000</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 27 Jan 2019 08:06:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.1.6</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>FOSSMeet @ NIT_Calicut</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Recently I had gone back to my college for convocation and believe me that place has got something that makes you feel right back at home every time you return back. All the old and tall buildings, trees, Rajpath, the long corridors of mechanical workshop, Aryabhatta, SSL (software systems lab), mens hostels, Main Canteen, Mini Canteen, Micro Canteen, Amul Canteen, Library Coffee shop, NLHC, ELHC, MB (Main Building), DB (Department Building) and list goes on. Though the academic experience differ for most of us but the hostel and campus experience for all the NITCians undoubtedly will be once in a lifetime experiences. I was fortunate to get some amazing seniors, juniors, professors, colleagues and most importantly some really good friends for life. Now let’s get back to the topic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During my convocation college visit, I got to meet our juniors once again and during the talks I was glad to hear that the work for next edition of FOSSMeet is in full swing. Yesterday it dawned on me that during my first year, when I saw the posters of FOSSMeet all around the campus, I went to CCC (Central Computing Center) to get more info about the event. To my surprise there were many blogs and articles describing the event from the participants and our seniors who conducted the previous versions of FOSSMeet. So I thought why not share my experience as a participant and as an organizer in different versions of FOSSMeet. And as one of my professor used to say “Documentation is the key”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a way I can say that my first introduction to FOSSMeet was from different articles and blogs I found online from my seniors which you can find it &lt;a href=&quot;http://srijanfoss2k16.blogspot.in/2016/02/fossmeetnitc-day1.html&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.j4v4m4n.in/category/nitc/&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://jacksonisaac.wordpress.com/tag/fossmeet-nitc/&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://anup07.wordpress.com/2014/07/11/fossmeet14-nit-calicut/&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://playingwithsid.blogspot.in/2008/04/fossmeet-nit-calicut-report.html&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://pramode.net/2008/04/08/report-on-fossschool-fossmeetnitc-2008/&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://sujithh.info/2009/03/fossmeetnitc-2009/&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; and many more. Though I had registered for FOSSMeet in my first year, I couldn’t take part in any events. Second year was the real deal. I remember John Chetan and Sudev Chetan with the gang came to our classes for induction. I can’t remember how I went to the meeting but I would say that was a turning point. It was full on fun. Me, Prasad, Leny, Reshma Sreekumar, Reshma Thomas, Aleena, Roshin, Vishnu, Francis, Kiran J Kumar (KJK), Kevin Jose (Dassapan) etc were the workforce and our seniors were the managers and our super seniors were the organizers (core committee members).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The best part of organizing FOSSMeet is not only the events that we can organize but also the people we meet and relationships we build out of it. During my second year FOSSMeet, we were assigned individual speakers whom we had to assist and solve any problems they raise. I was assigned Mr Ershad Kunnakkadan. He is a cool, humble and brilliant person. So I had not much of trouble assisting him. And I was fortunate to learn so much from him and get inspired by his humility. There is another person who inspired me, it was Mr Pirate Praveen. He is an alumnus of NIT Calicut and one of the organizers of the first ever FOSSMeet. His dedication and passion for free and Open Source software is really commendable. And we were proud to carry forward what he started. We can just go on speaking about such amazing folks who are carrying the baton and spreading the philosophy of FOSS. Another such person is Mr. Noufal Ibrahim. He is a genius.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After FOSSMeet ‘14, there was a year drop as our senior batch couldn’t pull it off due to some technical reasons. It was tough job for us to start again after a year drop as we could face difficulties for getting permissions from college authorities, sponsorship deals etc. But we decided to do it together. The first thing we did was contacting our beloved seniors. And we were overwhelmed by their response. They all shared the same enthusiasm and passion. Mr. Sudev, one of the core members of FOSSMeet ‘14 invited us to Bangalore. Mr Hari C M and Hasgeek hosted a small session regarding how to conduct FOSSMeet ‘16 in a way which was meaningful and devoid of all the mistakes they committed. Again we were overwhelmed by the response we got there. We were finding very hard finding sponsorship even after 3 months of work and that event changed everything. Two days later Mr Jaseem Abid sent a mail which solved that problem too. And like that we got our much needed financial support from Concur Technologies which also has some of NIT Calicut alumnus working there. And all this would have been a waste if we hadn’t got our much needed support from our faculty in charge. Though we were searching and we all had only one name in mind, Mr Vinod Pathari. I believe he is one of the best professors of our college. And I could say every CSE student of our college will second that. In all the troubles he was a mentor and guide to us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All this was possible only with the help of our seniors, juniors, professors, friends etc. Yes conducting meaningful events during FOSSMeet matters. But I believe the real learning for me was outside the event halls when Interacting with the speakers, attendees of the event etc. Sharing the knowledge is what its all about. So don’t miss out the opportunity where you can meet some of the brightest and passionate hackers you have seen.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://vasthav.github.io/articles/2016-10/fossmeet-2016-at-nit-calicut</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://vasthav.github.io/articles/2016-10/fossmeet-2016-at-nit-calicut</guid>
        
        <category>fossmeet</category>
        
        <category>nitc</category>
        
        <category>nit</category>
        
        <category>calicut</category>
        
        <category>FOSS</category>
        
        <category>foss</category>
        
        <category>free and open source</category>
        
        <category>Linux</category>
        
        <category>gnome</category>
        
        <category>golang</category>
        
        <category>kde</category>
        
        <category>Richard stallman</category>
        
        <category>praveen</category>
        
        
        <category>article</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What&#39;s new in Ubuntu 16.10 (Yakkety Yak)</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;whats-new&quot;&gt;What’s New?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After 6 months of development we can finally download &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ubuntu.com/download/desktop&quot;&gt;Ubuntu 16.10&lt;/a&gt;, the latest stable release of the world’s most popular desktop Linux distribution. The previous LTS(long Term Support) version, Ubuntu 16.04 (Xenial Xerus), was released back in April 2016. The new version is not a big update compared to the previous one but does come with some cool new features and updates. Ubuntu 16.10 will be supported for 9 months until July 2017. If you need Long Term Support, it is recommended you use Ubuntu 16.04 LTS instead. Find the links to release notes for official flavors &lt;a href=&quot;https://wiki.ubuntu.com/YakketyYak/ReleaseNotes#Official_flavours&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;updated-packages&quot;&gt;Updated Packages&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Linux kernel 4.8&lt;/strong&gt;
Ubuntu 16.10 is based on the Linux release series 4.8. And the new &lt;strong&gt;gpg&lt;/strong&gt; binary is now provided by &lt;strong&gt;gnupg2&lt;/strong&gt;. The Linux kernel 4.8 features numerable improvements to system stability, performance, power efficiency, and file system handling, including:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Support for over-clocking AMD graphic cards&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Initial NVIDIA Pascal support in Nouveau driver&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Raspberry Pi 3 SoC support&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;ACPI Low-Power Idle support&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Support for the Microsoft Surface 3 touch screen&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Wider range of audio device, USB and webcam drivers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;New versions of Apps&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Nautilus 3.20&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Firefox 48 web browser&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;LibreOffice 5.2 productivity suite&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Unity 8 Developer Preview&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Amazing new wallpapers&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Thunderbird 45&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Ubuntu Software 3.20&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Rhythmbox 3.4.1&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;GNOME Terminal 3.20&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Shotwell 0.22 and many more…&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;how-to-get-ubuntu-1610&quot;&gt;How to get Ubuntu 16.10&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;download-from-official-sources&quot;&gt;Download from official sources&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can download Ubuntu 16.10 .iso for 32-bit and 64-bit hardware using the links below.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;http://releases.ubuntu.com/16.10/ubuntu-16.10-desktop-i386.iso&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ubuntu 16.10 .iso for 32-bit&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt; 
&lt;a href=&quot;http://releases.ubuntu.com/16.10/ubuntu-16.10-desktop-amd64.iso&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ubuntu 16.10 .iso for 64-bit&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You can download ISOs and flashable images from from:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://releases.ubuntu.com/16.10/&quot;&gt;http://releases.ubuntu.com/16.10/&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;(Ubuntu Desktop and Server)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://cdimage.ubuntu.com/ubuntu/releases/16.10/&quot;&gt;http://cdimage.ubuntu.com/ubuntu/releases/16.10/&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;(Less Popular Ubuntu Images)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://cloud-images.ubuntu.com/releases/16.10/&quot;&gt;http://cloud-images.ubuntu.com/releases/16.10/&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;(Ubuntu Cloud Server)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://cdimage.ubuntu.com/netboot/16.10/&quot;&gt;http://cdimage.ubuntu.com/netboot/16.10/&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;(Ubuntu Netboot)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://cdimage.ubuntu.com/kubuntu/releases/16.10/&quot;&gt;http://cdimage.ubuntu.com/kubuntu/releases/16.10/&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;(Kubuntu)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://cdimage.ubuntu.com/lubuntu/releases/16.10/&quot;&gt;http://cdimage.ubuntu.com/lubuntu/releases/16.10/&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;(Lubuntu)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://cdimage.ubuntu.com/ubuntustudio/releases/16.10/&quot;&gt;http://cdimage.ubuntu.com/ubuntustudio/releases/16.10/&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;(Ubuntu Studio)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://cdimage.ubuntu.com/ubuntu-gnome/releases/16.10/&quot;&gt;http://cdimage.ubuntu.com/ubuntu-gnome/releases/16.10/&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;(Ubuntu GNOME)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://cdimage.ubuntu.com/ubuntukylin/releases/16.10/&quot;&gt;http://cdimage.ubuntu.com/ubuntukylin/releases/16.10/&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;(Ubuntu Kylin)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://cdimage.ubuntu.com/ubuntu-mate/releases/16.10/&quot;&gt;http://cdimage.ubuntu.com/ubuntu-mate/releases/16.10/&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;(Ubuntu MATE)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://cdimage.ubuntu.com/xubuntu/releases/16.10/&quot;&gt;http://cdimage.ubuntu.com/xubuntu/releases/16.10/&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;(Xubuntu)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;upgrading-from-ubuntu-1604-lts&quot;&gt;Upgrading from Ubuntu 16.04 LTS&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To upgrade on a desktop system:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Open the “Software &amp;amp; Updates” Setting in System Settings.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Select the 3rd Tab called “Updates”.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Set the “Notify me of a new Ubuntu version” drop down menu to “For any new version”.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Press Alt+F2 and type in “update-manager -d” (without the quotes) into the command box.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Update Manager should open up and tell you: New distribution release ‘16.10’ is available.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Click Upgrade and follow the on-screen instructions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://vasthav.github.io/articles/2016-10/whats-new-in-ubuntu-16-10</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://vasthav.github.io/articles/2016-10/whats-new-in-ubuntu-16-10</guid>
        
        <category>ubuntu</category>
        
        <category>16.1</category>
        
        <category>yakkety yak</category>
        
        <category>linux</category>
        
        <category>FOSS</category>
        
        <category>open source</category>
        
        <category>unix</category>
        
        <category>free</category>
        
        <category>canonical</category>
        
        <category>tutorial</category>
        
        
        <category>Tutorial</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Rest in Peace, my friend!</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Monday morning me and my friend Kiran were going on a bike to Calicut Medical College to see our friend for the last time, though Kiran was driving the bike, I was sure so many things might also have went through his mind too, as I was simply not able to control my emotions. All the pain, confusion, frustration and anger were so high that I was feeling really bad. When I was small, I had seen my grandfather die in front of me due to heart attack. After that also I have seen many dead bodies of people I cared about. So I thought that I could be strong to see him.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have great respect for our Prof. Muralikrishnan sir, the way he teaches and the way he gets into the details of each topic and the clarity that he has of the subject matter. But when I saw him in the medical college, the respect doubled. Friends said he was there throughout the three days. I just couldn’t look at Venkat’s father though. He was crying and crying. His eyes were red and his face had become so small. Some of my friends told me that he just couldn’t take the agonizing pain and also tried to commit suicide. But by God’s grace, he recovered.
Then the mortuary staff came out holding the stretcher. And I saw Venkat lying covered with the white cloth and the whole environment went so strange. When I looked at his face suddenly a strange thought went through my mind like a lightning that it could have been me or my friend Kiran or Roshin or Ashwin or as matter of fact it could have been any NITCian. I thought why HIM? He was the first person from his village in Andhra Pradesh who dared to come out of his village for higher studies. His financial background is so bad that the whole village contributed to his studies. Now the people from his village will think twice before sending their sons and daughters for studies outside the village. Because of this tragic event not just the dreams of his parents but also the dreams of a whole village are lost. Sometimes life is &lt;strong&gt;JUST NOT FAIR&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The question &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;‘why him?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; ’ was really haunting me. He was a real good person. Not a single person he knew had anything bad to say about him. He was happy go lucky. He was just playing gali cricket with his friends with this squash/tennis practicing wall as the wicket. He was batting and he hit the ball, suddenly his friends noticed the wall falling. They shouted “the wall’s falling!” Two others who were standing close to him ran and were able to come out but he couldn’t. He had a small problem with his leg. He was physically disabled. So he couldn’t run fast. He only had his three fingers outside the fallen wall. If he could have managed to take two more steps he could have saved his life. Those who took him to the hospital said that he so badly smashed that they couldn’t hold him on their lap so they made him lie on the floor of the auto rickshaw that they had hired. Nobody deserves such a death.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;They shouted “the wall’s falling!” Two others who were standing close to him ran and were able to come out but he couldn’t.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-protest&quot;&gt;The Protest&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The day when Venkat died all the students of NITC gathered in front of the person’s bungalow &lt;strong&gt;“whose name shall not be taken”&lt;/strong&gt; asking for justice. Our student representatives and some good professors, who really cared about the students they teach, went and prepared a list of demands. Some of them were to met by Monday evening and result shall be reported to the students in meeting in the OAT (open air theater) same evening. From the medical college we went back to college. By the time all students were wearing black to show their sadness and were ready for a peaceful protest for justice. For our brother. Initially the person was not ready to talk to the students. Later he changed his mind. Then he changed the venue. Though the students were not happy about it but they were only there to get their demands satisfied, the venue didn’t matter. He just came and sat there and was not talking to students. Some of my friends who were there in the hospital for three days told me that they had not seen an inhuman person like him. They said he stood there in the corridor of mortuary for 3 hours and then went and sat in his AC car. But when his parents arrived He didn’t even come out of his car to talk to his parents.
The meeting started. Some of us expected, but to the surprise of large multitude a battalion of POLICE was called and they created a perimeter. But we were not scared. All NITCians had only one target in mind. And that &lt;strong&gt;**&lt;/strong&gt;* sat their laughing. We didn’t get what was so funny. Another couple of professors who in their RAGAM and TATHVA speeches addressed us as precious students were laughing and commenting bullshit on the spot of tragedy. These things led to great agitation among the students. He didn’t came to mic and address us. As the students booed and started shouting he picked his a** and said “students everything is resolved and tomorrow you all go to your classes”. That’s it. With all this the students started losing their patience. Then another professor as a representative started about the agendas that we had demanded 2 days back on the day when we gathered in front of his house. What we all NITCians wanted was the report of things done and how they are done and the deadline until when it will be done if they required more time. It’s as simple as that. For that they were just giving round round answers. Students were not satisfied. We were asking questions but they were not giving any direct and satisfactory answers. This continued for about 3 hours and only 3 out of 8 agendas were discussed and they went inside and locked themselves.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In that time some students party people came to take advantage of the situation. But to their surprise nobody moved. All NITCians knew what they wanted and what they stood for and worked for the last 3 days. So they went as they came. Some fool took a stone and threw at a window. It didn’t cause even a scratch to glass. But our “brave and courageous hero whose name shall not be taken” declared that the college was suspended for indefinite period. And the whole college was asked to leave the college within 12 hours.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now the question is where is justice done? What we wanted was just justice for our brother who lost his life due to negligence of some higher authorities. The issue of the 10 degree leaning of the wall was even raised by the faculty just 3 months ago. Even after that also no action was taken. Is this too much to ask? Some of our seniors who fought and leaded us from the beginning of the event are now the new victims. Our honorable hero has sent a clear message to all of us that nobody can touch him. And he can suppress anyone with his political influence. Anyway who gives a f*** . His message to his people is “SCORE OR DIE SCORING”. But we NITCians have an answer for that and will be given soon.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://vasthav.github.io/articles/2014-02/rest-in-peace-my-friend</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://vasthav.github.io/articles/2014-02/rest-in-peace-my-friend</guid>
        
        <category>nitc</category>
        
        <category>rip</category>
        
        <category>suspended</category>
        
        
        <category>article</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Let it fly</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Things that i am not having today but will one day…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Everyone of us will definitely have some small dreams in their hearts that keep them going. Everyone of us might have some small dreams that gives them enough strength to fight with the troubles of today for the surprises and gifts of tomorrow. This may be a thing, a place, a special journey, becoming something, owning something or even being with a person that they cherished for a lifetime.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This things may not be seeming to be ever going to occur ever in near distant future but that’s the thrill in it. That’s  what God has made it to be. Then only we mankind will keep on moving and achieving our goals against all odds.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;As said by legend Mr. Milkha Singh, “a person with strong will power, hard-work, passion, for him sky is the limit..”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I also have some small dreams that I envision to make come true one day. And I believe that &lt;strong&gt;‘I CAN’&lt;/strong&gt;, one day. As said by legend Mr. Milkha Singh, “a person with strong will power, hardwork, passion, for him sky is the limit..”&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://vasthav.github.io/articles/2013-08/let-it-fly</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://vasthav.github.io/articles/2013-08/let-it-fly</guid>
        
        <category>dreams</category>
        
        <category>passion</category>
        
        <category>article</category>
        
        
        <category>article</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
