<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Vasthav&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Vasthav&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>©2019 Vasthav.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Jul 2020 09:57:25 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Udacity Data Science Nano Degree - Starbuck&#39;s Capstone Challenge</title>
      <link>/posts/udacity-dsnd-starbucks-capstone-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jul 2020 09:57:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/udacity-dsnd-starbucks-capstone-project/</guid>
      <description>Introduction As part of the Udacity - Data Science Nano Degree program I recently completed a task where I had to use a given data set, analyse it and come up with heuristics based recommendations. This blog post will present the final conclusions and recommendations I came up with after the analysis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why We Need a Mental Shift to Overcome Covid Induced Anxiety</title>
      <link>/posts/why-we-need-a-mental-shift-to-overcome-covid-induced-anxiety/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2020 17:09:44 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/why-we-need-a-mental-shift-to-overcome-covid-induced-anxiety/</guid>
      <description>The lockdown and quarantine have taken a psychological toll on many of us. The irony is that humans, being social animals, longs for companionship, which is exactly what we are sacrificing to survive this pandemic. So what is the answer to all this? What can we do to survive this anxious time?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Finding price trends and top neighbourhoods for affordable stays using Seattle Airbnb data</title>
      <link>/posts/seattle-airbnb-2016-data-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2020 15:17:26 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/seattle-airbnb-2016-data-analysis/</guid>
      <description>Introduction As part of the Udacity - Data Science Nano Degree program I recently completed a task where I had to use a given data set, analyse it and ask between 3-5 questions related to the business or real-world context of the data. And then each question must be answered with appropriate visualization, table, or statistic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An Honest Letter to My 16 Year Old Self</title>
      <link>/posts/a-honest-letter-to-my-16-years-old-self/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2020 16:53:48 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/a-honest-letter-to-my-16-years-old-self/</guid>
      <description>Dear Vasthav,
Trust me I know exactly how you feel. With just a few more days to go for your board exams, you have already started to feel the heat. You have stopped enjoying the process. And the thoughts of moving to Kerala after 10th feels like pulling yourself out of the mud with your roots and identity still firmly holding to Nasik.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top 5 things to do to maximize your productivity working remotely</title>
      <link>/posts/top-5-things-to-maximise-productivity-while-working-remotely/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2020 00:46:07 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/top-5-things-to-maximise-productivity-while-working-remotely/</guid>
      <description>With Companies like GitLab, Zapier, Automattic leading the way with 100% fully distributed employee base, there is a complete shift happening especially in tech space moving from traditional factory employee style of working that still, a large set of companies are stuck at.
Employees enjoy more flexibility in their daily life (spending time with their loved ones and on personal projects) with the time and money saved from long commutes and office rentals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fossmeet 2016 at Nit Calicut</title>
      <link>/posts/fossmeet-2016-at-nit-calicut/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2016 12:52:49 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/fossmeet-2016-at-nit-calicut/</guid>
      <description>Recently I had gone back to my college for convocation and believe me that place has got something that makes you feel right back at home every time you return back. All the old and tall buildings, trees, Rajpath, the long corridors of mechanical workshop, Aryabhatta, SSL (software systems lab), men&#39;s hostels, Main Canteen, Mini Canteen, Micro Canteen, Amul Canteen, Library Coffee shop, NLHC, ELHC, MB (Main Building), DB (Department Building) and list goes on.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>